Guide to the Terry Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Other Family Members, 1795-1939; Series VI; 1.75 linear feet (4 boxes)
  - Hughes, Robert Patterson
    - Roster of 1st Connecticut Regiment, 1898 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Roster of 3rd Connecticut Regiment, 1898 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Newsclippings, 1903-1909 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Newspapers: Harper's Weekly, 1899 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Terry, Alfred
    - Correspondence: Terry, Adrian, 1856, 1863 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Advertisement for his law practice, undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Terry, Alfred Howe (1875-1965) (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Terry, Clarissa Howe (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Terry, Harriet W.
    - Correspondence: Terry Adrian, 1879 September 26 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Terry, Alfred Howe (1875-1965)
    - Correspondence: Terry, Adrian, 1879 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence: Terry, Alfred H., 1881-1882, 1890 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence: Terry, Eliza Howe, 1868 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence: Terry, Harriet W., 1893 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Terry, Clarissa (Howe)
    - Correspondence: Terry Adrian, 1861-1867 (Box 11, Folder 28-29)
    - Correspondence: Terry, Alfred Howe, 1860-1863 (Box 11, Folder 30-32)
    - Correspondence: Terry, Harriet W., 1862-1863 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence: Terry, Jeremiah Wadsworth, 1864 October 16 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence: Terry, Robert G., 1859 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence: general, 1828-1862 (Box 11, Folder 36-37)
  - Terry, Frances
    - Correspondence: Hughes, Clara H. (Terry), 1878 August 8 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence: Terry, Alfred Howe, 1860-1887 (Box 11, Folder 39-43)
    - Correspondence: general, 1890-1917 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Tribute to Alfred Howe Terry by Livingston W. Cleaveland, 1903 June 7 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Newsclippings, 1869-1890, undated (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Terry, Harriet W.
    - Correspondence: Terry, Adrian, 1879-1885 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Correspondence: Terry, Alfred Howe, 1879 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Correspondence: Terry, Eliza Howe, 1880, undated (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Notes on family history, Circa 1936-1939 (Box 11, Folder 50)
      General
      See also: Terry Family Papers, donor file
  - Terry, James, (1823-1870): correspondence, 1855-1869 (Box 11, Folder 51-58)
  - Terry, James, (1844-1919)
    - Correspondence, 1898 (Box 11, Folder 59)
    - Correspondence: American Museum of Natural History, "Jade Boulder" controversy, 1905-1906 (Box 11, Folder 60)
    - Diaries, 1875-1877 (Box 11, Folder 61)
    - Diaries, 1878-1902 (Box 12, Folder 62-69)
    - Diaries, 1903-1912 (Box 13, Folder 70-72)
    - Writings, 1906 July (Box 13, Folder 73)
    - Miscellaneous accounts, 1859-1901 (Box 13, Folder 74)
  - Terry, Jeremiah Wadsworth
    - Correspondence: Terry, Adrian, 1888-1891 (Box 13, Folder 75)
    - Correspondence: Terry, Alfred Howe, 1872-1889 (Box 13, Folder 76)
    - Correspondence: Terry, Jane Russell, 1897 (Box 13, Folder 77)
    - Memorial program, 1905 (Box 13, Folder 78)
    - Printed matter, Circa 1897 (Box 13, Folder 79)
  - Terry, Josephine [Mrs. Jeremiah Wadsworth]: correspondence, 1870 (Box 13, Folder 80)
  - Terry, Nathaniel: indenture, 1795 September 7 (Box 13, Folder 81)
  - Terry, Robert Goldsborough
    - Correspondence: Terry, Alfred Howe, 1862 (?) (Box 13, Folder 82)
    - Correspondence: Terry, Harriet Wadsworth, 1877 (Box 13, Folder 83)
    - Legal notices, 1896-1897 (Box 13, Folder 84)
    - Account of journey to Kansas, 1859 (Box 13, Folder 85)
    - Photograph, undated (Box 13, Folder 85)
  - Terry Family: photographs, unidentified, undated (Box 13, Folder 86-87)
  - Wadsworth Family: "Red House, An Account of the Wadsworth Family Compiled and Annotated by the Late Mrs. Johnson, née Ellen Terry," Tms, undated (Box 13, Folder 88)
  - Wadsworth, Daniel: estate papers, newsclippings, 1879-1883 (Box 13, Folder 89)
  - Whittlesey, Almira Canning Cowles: obituary, 1902 December (Box 13, Folder 90)
  - Wright, Albert A.
    - Correspondence, 1860, 1877 (Box 13, Folder 91)
    - Legal deeds, 1834-1849 (Box 13, Folder 92)
    - Papers relating to his medical studies, 1827-1830 (Box 13, Folder 93)
  - Wright, Sarah
    - Correspondence: Cowles, Frances (Smith), 1874-1877, undated (Box 13, Folder 94)
    - Correspondence: general, 1885-1886 (Box 13, Folder 95)
  - Unidentified
    - Prescription for cure of cholera, undated (Box 13, Folder 96)
    - Notes, newspaper clippings, 1881-1916 (Box 13, Folder 96)